Finding Aid for the Photographers' Collection LSC.0098
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Shelflist
  - Fein, Philip: Architectural photographs. San Francisco, 1950-1958.; 3 boxes. 8 x 10 photographs, 4 x 5 negs. (Box 113, Box 114, Box 115)
    - Nunn & Bush Shoe Store, San Francisco, remodeling by Hertzska & Knowles, San Francisco., 1955.; 11 photographs. (Neg. #J110: 13 4 x 5, 1 2½ x 4½) (Box 113)
    - Johnson & Johnson Bldg., Palo Alto, by Ward & Bolles, San Francisco., 1955.; 13 photographs. (Neg. #J112: 11) (Box 113)
    - Mausoleum, Stockton or Santa Rosa, Hertzska & Knowles., 1955.; 11 photographs. (Neg. #J116: 9) (Box 113)
    - Macy's/Blum's, San Francisco, by Fink & Schindler, San Francisco., 1955.; 5 photographs. (Neg. #J184: 5) (Box 113)
    - Joseph Magnin's, San Francisco, by Fink & Schindler, San Francisco., 1955.; 2 photographs. (Neg. #J189: 5) (Box 113)
    - Century Savings & Loan, Santa Monica, by Bank Bldg. & Equip't. Corp., 1955.; 9 photographs. (Neg. #J193: 8) (Box 113)
    - Frank D. Stout, Interior Designs, San Francisco Peninsula., 1956.; 7 photographs. (Neg. #K59: 8) (Box 113)
    - Redwood City Hall of Justice, by Michael Goodman, Berkeley., 14 photographs. (Neg. #L46: 18) (Box 113)
    - Modesto Irrigation District Bldg., by Mitchell van Bourg, Berkeley., 1957.; 10 photographs. (Neg. #L47: 14) (Box 113)
    - Alameda Clinic, by Arthur Anderson., 20 photographs. (Neg. #L48: 20) (Box 113)
    - Electrical Workers Union #6, San Francisco, by Pitts Plate Glass., 1957.; 4 photographs. (Neg. #L106: 4) (Box 113)
    - Stanford University. Moore Hall, Women's Residence, by Milton Pfleuger., 1957.; 21 photographs. (Neg. #L107: 15) (Box 113)
    - Mendocino Hospital, by Stone & Mulloy., 17 photographs. (Neg. #L111: 10) (Box 114)
    - Bakersfield Hospital, by Stone & Mulloy., 1957.; 16 photographs. (Neg. #L112: 26) (Box 114)
    - Mel Neilson house, Crescent City, by Fivgado & Klein., 1957.; 3 photographs. (Neg. #L142: 5) (Box 114)
    - Seaside Hospital, Crescent City, by Fivgado & Klein., 1957.; 6 photographs. (Neg. #L144: 6) (Box 114)
    - Dows Prarie School, Arcata, by Van Bourg & Assoc., Berkeley., 1957.; 14 photographs. (Neg. #L145: 11) (Box 114)
    - Crescent City Court House, by Van Fleet, Eureka., 1957.; 8 photographs. (Neg. # L146: 13) (Box 114)
    - First Western Bank, Crescent City., 1957.; 1 photograph. (Neg. #L149: 2) (Box 114)
    - Shriners' Hospital, San Francisco, by Slone & Mulloy, San Francisco., 1957.; 14 photographs. (Neg. #L152: 12) (Box 114)
    - Pacific High School, San Leandro (model), by Schmidts, Hardman, & Wong, Berkeley., 1957.; 8 photographs. (Neg. #L157: 6) (Box 114)
    - Co-Op Market, Walnut Creek, by Hashiro Yuasa, Berkeley., 1958.; 8 photographs. (Neg. #M8: 8) (Box 114)
    - San Ramon Valley Church, by White & Herman, San Francisco., 1958.; 7 photographs. (Neg. #M9: 18) (Box 114)
    - Industrial Indeminity Bldg., Fresno, by White & Herman, San Francisco., 1958.; 27 photographs. (Neg. #M10: 22) (Box 114)
    - St. John's School, by Vincent Buckley, San Francisco., 1958.; 3 photographs. (Neg. #M12: 4) (Box 114)
    - First Congregational Church, Redwood City, by H. Kingsford Jones, Menlo Park., 1958.; 14 photographs. (Neg. #M16: 19) (Box 114)
    - Tulare County Court House., 14 photographs. (Neg. #M40: 13) (Box 114)
    - Stanley Nelson house, Visalia., 19 photographs. (Neg. #M42: 20) (Box 114)
    - Shottuch home, Junea, Alaska., 1958.; 10 photographs. (neg. #93: 15) (Box 114)
    - United Market, San Rafael, by Van der Ploeg, San Francisco., 15 photographs: 8 black & white, 7 color. (Neg. #P95: 12 black & white, 8 color 4 x 5, 2 color 2¼ x 3¼) (Box 114)
    - Alfred Dunhill Store, San Francisco., 9 photographs. (Neg. #S20: 20) (Box 114)
    - Negatives. (Box 115)
  - Feldman, Stanley J. *, 28 items. Photographs. Most of these images are mounted salon prints. (Box 17)
    - [Lilies], undated.
    - "At Lake Tahoe, Summer 1979"
    - "At Glacier Point, High Sierras, California", 1979
    - "Mount Whitney from Whitney Portal", 1977
    - "Chris", 1976
    - [Freeway overpasses], 1974
    - "Facade, Los Angeles Municipal Art Museum", 1976
    - "Ranch, Piru, California", 1972
    - "Bunche Hall, University of California, Los Angeles", 1973
    - "Grade and Curve, Soledad Canyon, California", 1965
    - "Virulence", 1964
    - "White Aspens and Stream, Big Tujunga, California", 1965
    - "Abandoned Farm, Above Northridge", 1966
    - "Quiet Stream, Big Tujunga, California", 1965
    - [High Voltage Tower], 1967
    - [Railroad cars], 1963
    - "Portrait in Sunlight, Beverly Truhan", 1966
    - "Devils Punchbowl, Outcroppings", 1965
    - "Patriarch Walnut", 1964
    - "Daniel at Play", 1964
    - "At Northridge, California", 1963
    - "Mission San Fernando, Morning Light", 1967
    - "Lighthouse, Point Loma, San Diego, California", undated.
    - "Mark", undated
    - "Topanga Canyon, Early Morning Light", 1964
    - "Portrait in Open Shade, Beverly Truhan", 1966
    - "White Aspens", 1965
    - "Three Sisters", 1967
  - Fellig, Arthur, 1 photograph. (Box 57)
  - Fellows, William B., 4 items. Photographs. (Box 58)
  - Figureida, George, 6 photographs. (Box 133)
  - Finely, Solomon Henderson, 84 glass negatives. (Box 120)
    Civil Engineer, began practice in Santa Ana, 1886; installed first municipal water system, 1891-1897; planned and built Modjeska Dam for Madam Modjeska, 1900; as Chief Engineer, built Santa Ana & Newport R.R., 1891-1899; planned and built five agricultural drainage districts in Orange County, 1889-1905; mayor of Santa Ana, 1902-1904; Chief Engineer, Orange County Highway Commission, 1915-1916; supervisor, Orange County, 1916-1928; organizer, 1928, and 1928-1944 secretary and director from Orange County for Metropolitan Water District of Southern California; member of California Commission to adjust Colorado river water claims with Arizona; Captain, 7th California Volunteers, Spanish American War, and 7th Regiment, California National Guard, 1904-1908. Who was who in America, volume 2, p.187.
    - Six views of "29" and "49 Palms," San bernardino, County, California, including one of an Indian camp showing squaws making baskets., 1897 February
    - Sixteen views of mines in (San Bernardino County?), 1897 February
      Includes two of the mining town of Vanderbilt, June 1896.
    - Six views of "Camp Santa Monica" showing 7th California Volunteers, Spanish American War, 1897 August
    - Twenty-nine views of Southern California, 1869-1897
      Includes the following:
      S.H. Finley and daughter
      W.K. Robinson's ranch
      Putting in casings on Chapman St. Bridge
      Railroad grading at Northam Avenue (Santa Ana & Newport R.R.?)
      Newport Beach wharf
      (Senator John P.?) Jones's residence
      Santa Monica, California
      San Bernardino Court House
      Unidentified buildings (Santa Ana?)
      Same showing parade (Los Angeles?)
      Highland Home Hotel near Beaumont, California
      View of Beaumony Valley from Highland Home Ranch
      Unidentified (Fort McArthur or fortifications, San Francisco?)
      Unidentified (San Francisco harbor with ships at anchor in foreground?)
      Colton Park, Colton, California
      First United Presbyterian Church, Los Angeles
      Unidentified steamship
      Unidentified bridge (near Santa Ana?)
      Unidentified dam
      Unidentified canal or bypass for dam
      Locomotive of the Santa Ana & Newport R.R. on the wharf at Newport Beach
      Residence of Miss Rhetta Jamieson, N.W. corner Whitmer and 6th Street, Los Angeles
      Newport Beach, Santa Ana & Newport R.R. office in background
      Serey Home in which Jessie Serrey lived over where Seccutio murdered "French Pete"
      Apricot drying at Foohill Road
      N.L. Brook's House, Arch Beach
      Reverend M.M. Kilpatrick's House (Santa Ana?)
      Samuel Hedge's Residence, 6221 East 1st Street, Los Angeles
      Tent of apricot pickers, Foothill Road
    - Twenty-nine views of schoolhouses in Santa Ana and (else where in Orange County?), 1896-1897
  - Fitzgibbon, J. H.: 2 headed girl, Millie Crissie. St. Louis, Mo., ca. 1869.; 1 item. 8.5 x 5.5 cm. Carte-de-visite. (Box 59)
    Photograph of two Black girls who were siamese twins.
  - Fleckenstein, Louis ***, 244 items. Photographs.
    Louis Fleckenstein was an early California Pictorialist, active ca. 1904-1940. His prints were exhibited throughout Europe and the U.S.
    - Salon Prints., Large images, chiefly 34.5 x 27 cm. 97 items.
      - "Rose Dance of the South.", 1915; Titled on mount beaneath image. Signed and dated 1915 on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Brita Eldh" (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Toronto, 1928; Stockholm, 1928; New Westminster, 1928; Antwerp, 1929; Dumfermline, 1929.
      - "Helen Castle.", Two copies. (Box 1)
      - "Bryce Canyon.", Signed on verso. Two copies. (Box 1)
      - "A Spanish Don.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Subject identified on verso as Charles Lummis.
      - "Descent from Mt. Whitney.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Four Score and Ten.", Signed on mount beneath image. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: The Camera Club, New York. undated.
      - "The Tambourine.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: V Salon Internacional de Fotografia de Madrid, 1925.
      - "Brooklyn, N.Y.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image.; Titled on verso, "Towers of Brooklyn," and signed. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Oklahoma Camera Club, undated; The Camera Club, New York, 1938; Omaha Camera Club, 1939-1940; Indianapolis Camera Club, undated; Camera Pictorialists, Kansas City, undated; Peoria Photo Forum, undated.
      - "Breezy Day on Telegraph Hill.", Signed on verso. Two copies. (Box 1)
      - "In the Vessel's Wake.", Signed on mount beneath image, and on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Fourth Annual Iowa Photographic Salon, Iowa State Fair, 1939.
      - "Reflections.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Rhythm in Solitude.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: V Salon Internacional de Fotografia de Madrid, 1925; Sixth Annual International Salon of Pictorial Photography held at the Provincial Exhibition of British Columbia, 1926.
      - "Tambourine Dance.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Say It with Flowers, She loves me, She loves me not.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: The London Salon of Photography, 1923; V Salon Internacional de Fotografia de Madrid, 1925.
      - "Hamadryad.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Burlesque.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Song Birdof the Hills.", Signed on verso and identified as Beth Beri, dancer. (Box 1)
      - "Miss N--", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Fifth Annual International Salon of Pictorial Photography, Provincial Exhibition, British Columbia, 1925.
      - "Yosemite Valley from Artist's Point.", Signed on mount beneath image, dated 1929. Two copies. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Portland Salon, 1929; Glasgow, Scotland, 1929; Sociedad Fotografica de Zargoza, Salon International, October, 1949.
        On permanent loan to the Grunwald Center for Graphic Arts.
      - "The Serenade.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "The Roll Collar.", Signed on verso. Two copies, one retouched. (Box 1)
      - "On the Edge of the Desert.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Jarabe.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Jungle Maid.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Los Angeles Camera Club, undated.
      - "The Major's Wife.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Internationella Fotografiutställningen, Stockholm, 1924.
      - "Burmese Dance.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: The London Salon of Photography, 1933.
      - "Nymphs of the Fountain.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Gaiety Under the Willows.", Signed on verso. Two copies, one medium size. (Box 1)
        [See Box 2.]
      - "A Contented Child.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Beth Beri.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Zaida.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Scotty's Castle--Death Valley.", Signed on verso. Two copies. (Box 1)
      - "Disc Thrower.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Pala Mission.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: The Camera Club, New York, 1938; Peoria Photo Forum, undated; Camera Pictorialists, Kansas City, undated; Indianapolis Camera Club, undated; Omaha Camera Club, 1939-1940; Oklahoma Camera Club, 1929.
      - "Dance Trio.", Presentation to Carl and Anna, signed on verso: "Louis, Christmas, 1935." (Box 1)
      - "Yosemite Falls.", Titled on mount beneath image. Titled on verso, "Yosemite Falls and Merced River," and signed. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Pacific International Salon of Photographic Art, Portland and Eugene, Oregon, 1929; Los Angeles Camera Club, 1929.
      - "Donaldina.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "My Friend Brookwell.", Signed on verso. Identified on verso as George Brookwell. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Pittsburgh Salon, 1919.
      - "Mexican Boy.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image. Two copies, one medium size. (Box 1)
      - "Excursionists--Lake Tahoe.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image. Two copies, one medium size. (Box 1)
      - "Bolero.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Canadian National Exhibition, 1927; The London Salon of Photography, 1929.
      - "Rita.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Character Study.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        [See Box 2--medium size images.]
      - "Portrait of a Boy.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Sixth Annual International Salon of Pictorial Photography, Provincial Exhibition, British Columbia, 1926.
      - "The Cave Woman.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Boy with Apple.", Signed on verso. Hand tinted. (Box 1)
      - "Beauty and the Beast.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Antics of Loki.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "The Echo.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Carmenta.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Vernal Falls, Yosemite.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Master David.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "The Gypsy.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Portrait of Miss D--.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Sixth Annual International Salon of Pictoria Photography, British Columbia, 1926.
      - "Aigrets.", Signed on back of mount. (Box 1)
      - "Mt. Lassen.", Signed on back of mount and beneath image. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Fourth Hobby Show, Long Beach, California, 1939; The Photographic Arts Society, Inc., Balboa Park, San Diego, California, undated.
      - "Red Rock Canyon Nacies.", Signed on back of mount and beneath image. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Fifth Hobby Show, Long Beach, California, 1940.
      - "A Canyon Bungalow.", Signed on back of mount and beneath image. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: The Photographic Arts Society, Inc., Balboa Park, San Diego, California, undated.
      - "The South Wind.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: VII Salon Internacional de Fotografia, Madrid, 1928.
      - "Gulls in Flight.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Beneath the Willows.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Pruitt Carter, Illustrator.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "The Fountain of Youth.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "A Knight and His Lady.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - "Strollers.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Dark-haired woman looking to her left. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Young girl with white bow in hair., Embossed Fleckenstein. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman with curly hair, dress with appliqué daisies., Two copies. (Box 1)
        One copy on permanent loan to the Grunwald Center for the Graphic Arts.
      - [Untitled.] Profile of woman with small hoop drop earring. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Brick house, car in driveway. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man with broad nose. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Girls in bathing suits, with numbers. (contest?). (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in pince-nez, pompadour hair-style. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Boy and girl reading together., 1922; Signed on image. Hand tinted. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Three girls sitting in grassy sand., Two copies. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Boy wearing cap with chin in hands. (Box 1)
        [See Box 2, image entitled,"On the Sidelines."]
      - [Untitled.] Los Angeles County Courhouse, shooting downward. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in large-brimmed dark straw hat. Identified on verso as Beth Beri, dancer., Two copies. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Beach encampment, people wading, fishing tents in background. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Group of dancers with long scarf, in garden. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] San Juan Capistrano Mission broken arches. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Bathers in tide pools. (Malibu?) (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man playing a baby grand piano. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Two women and dog on beach. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Girl in bathing suit reaching toward boy in shepherd costume. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Two men fishing on beach. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Haystacks in field. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman wearing shawl. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in dark dress with lace collar. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Canyon walls. Identifed on verso as Zion Canyon., Two copies. (Box 1)
        One copy on permanent loan to the Grunwald Center for Graphic Arts.
      - [Untitled.] Charles Lummis., Hand tinted portrait. (Box 1)
      - "Young America.", Signed. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Young boy in hat. (Box 1)
    - Small images, chiefly, 16 x 11 cm. 26 items.
      - [Untitled.] Young woman., On Fleckenstein mount. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Young girl yawning., Oval-shaped photograph. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Women playing baseball. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in art deco necklace. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman playing mandolin. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man holding violin. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in flowered bonnet., On Fleckenstein mount. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman holding camelia. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman with large vase and calla lily., Embossed Fleckenstein. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Two Dutch girls., On Fleckenstein mount. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Two Dutch girls (different pose from above)., On Fleckenstein mount. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman standing at door, hand on knob. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Three women and two men on mountain walk, first woman with a camera. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Sheep grazing beneath tree. (Box 1)
      - "Haytime.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Three cows in pasture. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man and woman., Signed on verso. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in high-necked dress with pleated yoke., On Fleckenstein mount. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in Greek gown, large vase behind her. (Box 1)
      - "Study of a head. Portrait in Gum.", Signed on verso. (Box 1)
        Exhibited: Cleveland Salon, 1904.
      - "Entrance to Oak Lodge.", 1916 (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man in cowboy hat and bandana. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Girl in large flowered hat. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Girl wearing a white hairbow with a kitten in her lap. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Ballerina with garland in her hair. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Man and woman on the beach with parasol. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman with flower basket. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in lace-trimmed dress with scarf tied around her head. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Middle-aged woman in large straw hat. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Tree and river. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Watching for the Fleet. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] Tahquitz Peak. (Box 1)
      - [Untitled.] 3/4 profile of woman wearing hat and lace collar. (Box 1)
    - Medium images, chiefly 20 x 24 cm. 112 items.
      - "An Old Settler.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Old Songs." (Box 2)
      - "Mexican Boy.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Race track scene. (Box 2)
      - "Mark Anthony.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Black Diamond Rattler.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Baby Dian.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
        Exhibited: The London Salon of Photography, 1934.
      - [Untitled.] Woman in sleeveless dress, holding rock. (Box 2)
      - "Florence--ca.1915." (Box 2)
      - "She loves me, she loves me not.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman playing mandolin. Identified on verso as Florence Bruxhom. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young girl in dress with gathered shoulder. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman in dress trimmed with Greek key design. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Same young woman, arms on back of chair. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Ballet dancer on pointe. (Box 2)
      - "Portrait--Mr. S.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
        Exhibited: Scottish National Salon, 1932.
      - "Eucalypti.", Titled and signed on mount beneath image. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Nude woman being "chased" by a Joshua Tree. (Box 2)
      - "The Weary Messenger.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Two women and a man at campfire. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Farm yard with wine tuns in arched doorway. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Farmyard with wine tuns in arched doorway. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Clouds in darkening sky. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Man playing violin. (Box 2)
      - "A Portrait.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman, back to camera, with feather fan., Embossed Fleckenstein. (Box 2)
      - "Wild Rose Canyon." (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in brimmed hat, small bouquet on table beside her., Embossed Fleckenstein. (Box 2)
      - "Curiosity.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "In Mortal Combat.", Titled and signed beneath image on mount. (Box 2)
      - "On the Sidelines.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Charles Lummis.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "An Oriental Visitor.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "The Muses.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - "The Wool Shawl.", 1907; Signed and dated 1907, on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Man with long hair and beard. (Box 2)
      - "Bas-Relief.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - Woman in fuzzy angora hat. (Box 2)
      - "A Wild-West Carnival.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman wearing large hoop earrings. (Box 2)
      - "Young Artist.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman reading to two young girls., Two copies. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman wearing heavy bead necklace and lace cumberbund. (Box 2)
      - "Bobbie's First Christmas, 1902." (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman playing piano, standing lamp in background., Embossed Fleckenstein. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Baby sitting in nest of tulle. (Box 2)
      - "Profile Portrait.", 1906 November; Signed and dated November, 1906, on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman, hair center-parted and pushed behind ear. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in elaborate coat with monkey tail trimming. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Indian with an "x" painted on cheek., Gum print. (Box 2)
      - "The Student.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
        Exhibited: Photo Era Annual Contest, Boston, 1905.
      - "Mission Street, San Gabriel.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Young woman with head covered with white veil. (Box 2)
      - "Just Kids--a Study.", 1931; Signed and dated 1931, on verso. (Box 2)
      - "Desider Josef Vescer.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Elderly black woman, head in bandana., Hand-colored. (Box 2)
      - "The Music Room.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Vernal Falls, Yosemite., 1929; Signed and dated 1929 on mount beneath image. (Box 2)
      - "Rico.", Signed on verso. (Box 2)
      - [Untitled.] Woman in white dress with black neck band. (Box 2)
      - "Nature Man of Palm Springs.", 1918; Signed and dated 1918, on verso. (Box 2)